<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Foodie</string>
    <string name="foodie" translatable="false">FOODIE</string>
    <string name="splash_screen_logo">splash screen logo</string>
    <string name="servings">Servings</string>
    <string name="servings_detail">%1$s servings</string>
    <string name="share_detail">%1$s \nIngredients:\n%2$s \n\nInstructions:\n%3$s</string>
    <string name="time">time</string>
    <string name="name">name</string>
    <string name="foodImage">foodImage</string>
    <string name="ingredientsText">ingredientsText</string>
    <string name="ingredients">Ingredients</string>
    <string name="instructions">Instructions</string>
    <string name="foodname">foodName</string>
    <string name="_4_person">4 person</string>
    <string name="_30_minutes">30 Minutes</string>
    <string name="action_profile">action_profile</string>
    <string name="_260_calories">260 Calories</string>
    <string name="instructionsText">instructionsText\n</string>
    <string name="profile_picture">profile picture</string>
    <string name="separator">separator</string>
    <string name="cooking_time">Cooking Time</string>
    <string name="share">Share</string>
    <string name="nama" translatable="false">nama</string>
    <string name="email" translatable="false">email</string>
    <string name="clock_icon">clock_icon</string>
    <string name="person_icon">person icon</string>
    <string name="calories_icon">calories icon</string>

    <string-array name="data_name">
        <item>Lasagna</item>
        <item>Vegetarian Bibimbap</item>
        <item>Miso Soup</item>
        <item>Fried Rice</item>
        <item>Chicken Satay</item>
        <item>Japchae</item>
        <item>Chicken Katsu</item>
        <item>Ketoprak</item>
        <item>Spaghetti Aglio Olio</item>
        <item>Bakso</item>
        <item>Beef Bulgogi</item>
        <item>Sushi</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="cook_time">
        <item>180 mins</item>
        <item>60 mins</item>
        <item>30 mins</item>
        <item>40 mins</item>
        <item>40 mins</item>
        <item>60 mins</item>
        <item>45 mins</item>
        <item>30 mins</item>
        <item>45 mins</item>
        <item>90 mins</item>
        <item>90 mins</item>
        <item>45 mins</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="servings">
        <item>12</item>
        <item>3</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>6</item>
        <item>2–3</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>6</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>8</item>
        <item>3–4</item>
        <item>8</item>
    </string-array>

    <integer-array name="data_photo">
        <item>@drawable/lasagna1</item>
        <item>@drawable/bibimbap2</item>
        <item>@drawable/miso3</item>
        <item>@drawable/nasigoreng4</item>
        <item>@drawable/sate5</item>
        <item>@drawable/japhae6</item>
        <item>@drawable/katsu7</item>
        <item>@drawable/ketoprak8</item>
        <item>@drawable/aglio9</item>
        <item>@drawable/bakso10</item>
        <item>@drawable/bulgogi11</item>
        <item>@drawable/sushi12</item>
    </integer-array>

    <string-array name="data_ingredients">
        <item>
            -	1 pound sweet Italian sausage
            \n-	¾ pound lean ground beef
            \n-	½ cup minced onion
            \n-	2 cloves garlic, crushed
            \n-	1 (28 ounce) can crushed tomatoes
            \n-	2 (6.5 ounce) cans canned tomato sauce
            \n-	½ cup water
            \n-	2 tablespoons white sugar
            \n-	2 (6 ounce) cans tomato paste
            \n-	4 tablespoons chopped parsley, divided
            \n-	1 ½ teaspoons dried basil leaves
            \n-	1 ½ teaspoons salt, divided, or to taste
            \n-	1 teaspoon Italian seasoning
            \n-	½ teaspoon fennel seeds
            \n-	¼ teaspoon ground black pepper
            \n-	12 lasagna noodles
            \n-	16 ounces ricotta cheese
            \n-	1 egg
            \n-	¾ pound mozzarella cheese, sliced
            \n-	¾ cup grated Parmesan cheese
        </item>

        <item>
            -	2 tablespoons sesame oil
            \n-	1 cup carrot matchsticks
            \n-	1 cup zucchini matchsticks
            \n-	½ (14 ounce) can bean sprouts, drained
            \n-	6 ounces canned bamboo shoots, drained
            \n-	1 (4.5 ounce) can sliced mushrooms, drained
            \n-	⅛ teaspoon salt to taste
            \n-	2 cups cooked and cooled rice
            \n-	⅓ cup sliced green onions
            \n-	2 tablespoons soy sauce
            \n-	¼ teaspoon ground black pepper
            \n-	1 tablespoon butter
            \n-	3 eggs
            \n-	3 teaspoons sweet red chili sauce, or to taste
        </item>

        <item>
            -	4 cups water
            \n-	2 teaspoons dashi granules
            \n-	3 tablespoons miso paste
            \n-	1 (8 ounce) package silken tofu, diced
            \n-	2 green onions, sliced diagonally into 1/2 inch pieces
        </item>


        <item>
            -	3 large eggs, beaten
            \n-	1 tablespoon vegetable oil
            \n-	1 onion, chopped
            \n-	1 leek, chopped
            \n-	2 green chile peppers, chopped
            \n-	1 clove garlic, minced
            \n-	½ pound skinless, boneless chicken breasts, cut into thin strips
            \n-	½ pound peeled and deveined shrimp
            \n-	1 teaspoon ground coriander
            \n-	1 teaspoon ground cumin
            \n-	3 cups cold cooked white rice
            \n-	3 tablespoons kecap manis (sweet soy sauce)
        </item>

        <item>
            -	¼ cup coconut milk
            \n-	2 tablespoons reduced sodium soy sauce
            \n-	2 ½ teaspoons yellow curry powder
            \n-	1 ½ teaspoons turmeric
            \n-	3 cloves garlic, minced
            \n-	1 tablespoon freshly grated ginger
            \n-	1 tablespoon brown sugar
            \n-	1 tablespoon fish sauce
            \n-	2 pounds boneless, skinless chicken thighs, cut into 1-inch chunks
            \n-	1 tablespoon canola oil
            \n-	Kosher salt and freshly ground black pepper, to taste
            \nFOR THE PEANUT SAUCE
            \n-	3 tablespoons creamy peanut butter
            \n-	1 tablespoon reduced sodium soy sauce
            \n-	1 tablespoon freshly squeezed lime juice
            \n-	2 teaspoons brown sugar
            \n-	2 teaspoons chili garlic sauce, or more
            \n-	1 teaspoon freshly grated ginger
        </item>

        <item>
            -	½ pound Korean dang myun noodles
            \n-	2 ½ teaspoons sesame oil, divided
            \n-	2 tablespoons soy sauce
            \n-	2 teaspoons white sugar
            \n-	1 tablespoon vegetable oil
            \n-	2 carrots, cut into match-stick size pieces
            \n-	½ pound asparagus, thinly sliced
            \n-	¾ cup thinly sliced onions
            \n-	2 cloves garlic, minced
            \n-	3 green onions cut into 1-inch pieces
            \n-	½ cup dried shiitake mushrooms, soaked until soft, then sliced into strips
            \n-   1 tablespoon sesame seeds
        </item>

        <item>
            -   1 pound boneless, skinless chicken breasts, pounded thin
            \n-   1 cup all-purpose flour
            \n-   1/2 cup panko bread crumbs
            \n-   1 egg, beaten
            \n-   1 tablespoon soy sauce
            \n-   1 tablespoon sesame oil
            \n-   1 tablespoon ground ginger
            \n-   1 teaspoon garlic powder
            \n-   1/4 teaspoon salt
            \n-   1/4 teaspoon black pepper
        </item>

        <item>
            -   10 ounces dried bean sprouts, rinsed and drained
            \n-   1 cucumber, peeled, seeded, and diced
            \n-   1/2 cup chopped peanuts, roasted and salted
            \n-   1/4 cup chopped green onions
            \n-   1/4 cup kecap manis (sweet soy sauce)
            \n-   1/4 cup sambal kacang (peanut sauce)
            \n-   2 hard-boiled eggs, sliced
            \n-   1/4 cup chopped fried shallots
            \n-   1/4 teaspoon salt
            \n-   1/4 teaspoon black pepper
        </item>

        <item>
            -   1 pound spaghetti
            \n-   1/4 cup extra-virgin olive oil
            \n-   4 cloves garlic, minced
            \n-   1/2 teaspoon red pepper flakes (optional)
            \n-   1/4 cup chopped fresh parsley
            \n-   Salt and pepper to taste
        </item>

        <item>
            -   500 grams ground beef (5% fat)
            \n-   1 egg
            \n-   5 cloves garlic, minced
            \n-   2 tablespoons tapioca flour
            \n-   1 tablespoon salt
            \n-   1/2 teaspoon white pepper
            \n-   1/4 teaspoon baking powder
            \n-   Water, as needed
        </item>

        <item>
            -	5 tablespoons soy sauce
            \n-	¼ cup chopped green onion
            \n-	2 ½ tablespoons white sugar
            \n-	2 tablespoons minced garlic
            \n-	2 tablespoons sesame seeds
            \n-	2 tablespoons sesame oil
            \n-	½ teaspoon ground black pepper
            \n-	1 pound flank steak, thinly sliced
        </item>

        <item>
            -   1 cup short-grain rice
            \n-   2 cups water
            \n-   2 tablespoons rice vinegar
            \n-   1 tablespoon sugar
            \n-   1 teaspoon salt
            \n-   2 sheets nori, cut into 8 equal strips
            \n-   1 avocado, peeled, pitted, and sliced
            \n-   1 cucumber, peeled and sliced
            \n-   1/2 cup cooked salmon, chopped
            \n-   1/4 cup mayonnaise
            \n-   1/4 teaspoon wasabi paste
            \n-   1/4 cup pickled ginger
        </item>

    </string-array>

    <!--Direction-->
    <string-array name="data_instructions">
        <item>
            1.  Gather all your ingredients.
            \n2.  Cook sausage, ground beef, onion, and garlic in a Dutch oven over medium heat until well browned.
            \n3.  Stir in crushed tomatoes, tomato sauce, tomato paste, and water.
            \n4.  Season with sugar, 2 tablespoons parsley, basil, 1 teaspoon salt, Italian seasoning, fennel seeds, and pepper.
            \n5.  Simmer, covered, for about 1 1/2 hours, stirring occasionally.
            \n6.  Bring a large pot of lightly salted water to a boil.
            \n7.  Cook lasagna noodles in boiling water for 8 to 10 minutes.
            \n8.  Drain noodles, and rinse with cold water.
            \n9.  In a mixing bowl, combine ricotta cheese with egg, remaining 2 tablespoons parsley, and 1/2 teaspoon salt.
            \n10. To assemble, spread 1 1/2 cups of meat sauce in the bottom of a 9x13-inch baking dish.
            \n11. Arrange 6 noodles lengthwise over meat sauce.
            \n12. Spread with 1/2 of the ricotta cheese mixture.
            \n13  Top with 1/3 of the mozzarella cheese slices.
            \n14  Spoon 1 1/2 cups meat sauce over mozzarella, and sprinkle with 1/4 cup Parmesan cheese.
            \n15. Repeat layers, and top with remaining mozzarella and Parmesan cheese.
            \n16. Cover with foil: to prevent sticking, either spray foil with cooking spray or make sure the foil does not touch the cheese.
            \n17.  Bake in the preheated oven for 25 minutes.
            \n18. Remove the foil and bake for an additional 25 minutes.
            \n19. Rest lasagna for 15 minutes before serving.
        </item>

        <item>
            1.	Heat sesame oil in a large skillet over medium heat
            \n2.  Cook and stir carrot and zucchini in the hot oil until vegetables begin to soften, about 5 minutes.
            \n3.  Stir in bean sprouts, bamboo shoots, and mushrooms. Cook and stir until carrots are tender, about 5 more minutes.
            \n4.  Season to taste with salt and set vegetables aside.
            \n5.	Stir cooked rice, green onions, soy sauce, and black pepper in the same skillet until the rice is hot.
            \n6.  In a separate skillet over medium heat, melt butter and gently fry eggs, turning once.
            \n7.  Until the yolks are still slightly runny but the egg whites are firm, about 3 minutes per egg.
            \n8.	To serve, divide hot cooked rice mixture between 3 serving bowls
            \n9.  Top each bowl with 1/3 of the vegetable mixture and a fried egg.
            \n10. Serve sweet red chili sauce on the side for mixing into bibimbap.
        </item>

        <item>
            1.  Combine water and dashi granules in a medium saucepan over medium-high heat; bring to a boil.
            \n2.  Reduce heat to medium and whisk in miso paste. Stir in tofu.
            \n3.  Separate the layers of green onions, and add them to the soup.
            \n4.  Simmer gently for 2 to 3 minutes before serving.
        </item>

        <item>
            1.	Heat a large nonstick skillet over medium heat.
            \n2.	Pour eggs into the hot skillet and cook until the edges begin to set.
            \n3.  Lift the edges to allow any uncooked egg to flow onto the hot pan, about 1 minute.
            \n5.  Flip omelet in one piece and cook until fully set, about 30 seconds.
            \n6.  Transfer omelet to a cutting board and slice into 1/2-inch strips. Set aside.
            \n7.	Heat vegetable oil in a wok or large frying pan over high heat.
            \n8.  Stir in onion, leek, chile peppers, and garlic.
            \n9.  Cook and stir until onion is soft, 3 to 5 minutes.
            \n10. Stir in chicken, shrimp, coriander, and cumin; mix well.
            \n11. Cook and stir for about 5 minutes.
            \n12.	Mix in cooked rice, sweet soy sauce, and omelet strips
            \n13. cook until rice is heated through and chicken is no longer pink in the center, 3 to 5 minutes.
        </item>

        <item>
            1.  To make the peanut sauce, whisk together peanut butter, soy sauce, lime juice, brown sugar, chili garlic sauce and ginger in a small bowl.
            \n2.  Whisk in 2-3 tablespoons water until desired consistency is reached; set aside.
	        \n3.  In a medium bowl, combine coconut milk, soy sauce, curry powder, \nturmeric, garlic, ginger, brown sugar and fish sauce.
	        \n4.  In a gallon size Ziploc bag or large bowl, combine chicken and coconut milk mixture; marinate for at least 2 hours to overnight, turning the bag occasionally.
	        \n5.  Drain the chicken from the marinade, discarding the marinade.
            \n6.  Preheat grill to medium high heat. Thread chicken onto skewers.
            \n7.  Brush with canola oil; season with salt and pepper, to taste.
            \n8.  Add skewers to grill, and cook, turning occasionally, until the chicken is completely cooked through
            \n9.  reaching an internal temperature of 165 degrees F, about 12-15 minutes.

        </item>

        <item>
            1.	Fill a large pot with lightly salted water and bring to a rolling boil.
            \n2.  Cook noodles in boiling water, stirring occasionally, until tender yet firm to the bite, 4 to 5 minutes.
            \n3.  Drain, then rinse with cold water.
            \n4.  Toss noodles with 1 teaspoon sesame oil; set aside.
            \n5.	Whisk together soy sauce and sugar in a small bowl; set aside.
            \n6.	Heat vegetable oil in a skillet over medium-high heat.
            \n7.  Cook and stir carrots, asparagus, onions, and garlic in hot oil until softened, about 5 minutes.
            \n8.  Stir in green onions and mushrooms; continue cooking and stirring for 30 seconds.
            \n9.	Pour in soy sauce mixture, then add noodles.
            \n10. Cook and stir until noodles are warmed through, 2 to 3 minutes.
            \n11. Remove from heat and toss with sesame seeds and remaining 1 1/2 teaspoons sesame oil.
            \n12. Japchae ready to serve
        </item>

        <item>
            1.  In a shallow bowl, whisk together the flour, panko bread crumbs, salt, and pepper.
            \n2.  In a separate shallow bowl, whisk together the egg, soy sauce, sesame oil, ginger, and garlic powder.
            \n3.  Dip the chicken breasts in the egg mixture, then in the breadcrumb mixture.
            \n4.  Heat the oil in a large skillet over medium heat.
            \n5.  Fry the chicken breasts in batches until golden brown and cooked through, about 5 minutes per side.
            \n6.  Serve with your favorite dipping sauce.
        </item>

        <item>
            1.  In a large bowl, combine the bean sprouts, cucumber, peanuts, green onions, kecap manis, sambal kacang, hard-boiled eggs, fried shallots, salt, and pepper.
            \n2.  Stir to combine.
            \n3.  Serve immediately.
        </item>

        <item>
            1.  Cook the spaghetti according to package directions.
            \n2.  While the spaghetti is cooking, heat the olive oil in a large skillet over medium heat.
            \n3.  Add the garlic and cook until softened, about 1 minute.
            \n4.  Add the red pepper flakes (if using) and cook for 1 minute more.
            \n5.  Drain the spaghetti and add it to the skillet with the garlic and oil.
            \n6.  Toss to coat.
            \n7.  Stir in the parsley, salt, and pepper.
            \n8.  Serve immediately.
        </item>

        <item>
            1.  In a large bowl, combine the ground beef, egg, garlic, tapioca flour, salt, white pepper, and baking powder. Mix well.
            \n2.  Add water, a tablespoon at a time, until the mixture is just combined.
            \n3.  Shape the mixture into meatballs, about 2 inches in diameter.
            \n4.  Bring a large pot of water to a boil.
            \n5.  Add the meatballs and cook for 10-15 minutes, or until cooked through.
            \n6.  Drain the meatballs
            \n7.  Serve with your favorite dipping sauce.

        </item>

        <item>
            1.  Gather all ingredients.
            \n2.  Whisk soy sauce, green onion, sugar, garlic, sesame seeds, sesame oil, and pepper together in a bowl.
            \n3.  Place flank steak slices in a shallow dish. Pour marinade over top.
            \n4.  Cover and refrigerate for at least 1 hour or overnight.
            \n5.  Preheat an outdoor grill for high heat, and lightly oil the grate.
            \n6.  Quickly grill flank steak slices on the preheated grill until slightly charred and cooked through, 1 to 2 minutes per side.
            \n7.  Serve hot and enjoy!
        </item>

        <item>
            1.  Rinse the rice in a fine-mesh strainer until the water runs clear.
            \n2.  Combine the rice and water in a saucepan.
            \n3.  Bring to a boil, then reduce heat to low and simmer for 15 minutes, or until the rice is cooked through.
            \n4.  Remove the rice from the heat and let it cool for 5 minutes.
            \n5.  In a small bowl, combine the rice vinegar, sugar, and salt.
            \n6.  Stir to dissolve the sugar and salt.
            \n7.  Add the rice vinegar mixture to the cooked rice and stir to combine.
            \n8.  Spread a sheet of nori on a bamboo rolling mat.
            \n9.  Spread a thin layer of rice over the nori, leaving a 1-inch border at the top and bottom.
            \n10. Place the avocado, cucumber, salmon, mayonnaise, wasabi paste, and pickled ginger on the rice.
            \n11. Starting at the bottom, roll the nori up tightly.
            \n12. Using a sharp knife, cut the sushi roll into 8 equal pieces.
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_calories">
        <item>313 calories</item>
        <item>462 calories</item>
        <item>59 calories</item>
        <item>237 calories</item>
        <item>338 calories</item>
        <item>348 calories</item>
        <item>192 calories</item>
        <item>509 calories</item>
        <item>249 calories</item>
        <item>325 calories</item>
        <item>664 calories</item>
        <item>165 calories</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>